(Penny:)you even made out with her
on a train.
(Sheldon:)She told you?
(Penny:)Of course she told me,
it's the most interesting thing
(Penny:)that's ever happened to
her in her entire life!
(Leonard:)You're too close to it,
but Amy has had a huge impact on you.
(Leonard:)You're right.
(Sheldon:)Without realizing it,
I've allowed that woman
(Sheldon:)to alter my personality.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, you didn't
have a personality,
(Leonard:)you just had some shows you liked.
(Penny:)No.
(Sheldon:)No, I've changed.
(Sheldon:)Like the frog who's put
in a pot of water
(Sheldon:)that's heated so gradually
(Sheldon:)he doesn't realize
he's boiling to death.
(Penny:)Or you're the frog who's
been kissed by a princess
(Penny:)and turned into a prince.
(Leonard:)Or you're just a tall, annoying frog.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)I have to break up
with my girlfriend.
(Penny:)-Sheldon, wait.
-No.
(Sheldon:)You've opened my eyes to the truth.
(Sheldon:)Amy has made me a more affectionate,
open-minded person.
(Sheldon:)And that stops now.